exxat.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy – Exxat

Exxat, LLC. (“Exxat”) operates several websites including exxat.com, apps.exxat.com, and support.exxat.com. It is Exxat’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Exxat collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Exxat’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Exxat’s visitors use its public & secure website. From time to time, Exxat may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Customers (Users) of Exxat’s services will be entering and storing data. Exxat may collect personally identifying information including, but not limited to, name, address phone, email, username, password, IP address during the process. Exxat will not share, distribute, or reference any such data except as may be required by law. Those who engage in transactions with Exxat – by purchasing access to the Exxat’s services, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Exxat collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Exxat. Exxat does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Each of Exxat’s clients agree to release information to configuring the product with the understanding that Exxat will only use this information for servicing the agreement with client.

Exxat’s products do not track any PHI (protected health information) about patients which is protected by HIPAA.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Exxat uses encrypted cookies to help Exxat identify and track visitors’ session, their usage of Exxat website, and their website access preferences. Exxat visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Exxat’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Exxat’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Links

Exxat’s site may contain links to other web sites which may have privacy policies different from Exxat’s and we encourage you to carefully read those policies. Exxat is not responsible for the contents of any such websites.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Exxat may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Exxat’s sole discretion. Exxat encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Feedback

If you have any comments about Exxat’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@exxat.com
